AGRE KOUADJO AMOS YANN EMMANUEL

Technical Support - Web and Software Developer

Nairobi - Kenya | +254(0)799673045 | <u>yannagre1997@gmail.com</u> | Single, No children https://www.linkedin.com/in/yann-emmanuel-agre-5a90a6194

PROFILE

Born and raised in Côte d'Ivoire with multicultural experiences in developing countries of Africa such as Ghana, South Africa and Kenya. Junior programmer, computers and IT resources management and administration. Undertaking a Bachelor degree in Business Information Technology. Polyglot, dedicated, growth oriented and knowledge seeker. Ready to avail my knowledge and skills to my future employers as well as having a good collaboration with my colleagues and clientele.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Administrative and IT Assistant (Intern) | Ophthalmic Centre Siloam | Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire | October 2020 – December 2020

- Daily record of expenses, patients' details
- Management of the medical inventory
- Management and maintenance of IT equipment
- Training and support to staff
- Development of a quotation format for patients
- Invoice deliveries to patients

Web Developer (Consultant/Intern) | Digital Oasis Ltd | Nairobi, Kenya | February 2020 – April 2020

- Assistance to the Development team with various projects
- Provision of Technical Support to clients as well as reinstalling Operating Systems and Software
- Training and mentoring of the technical staff

Technical Support Assistant (Consultant) | Ophthalmic Centre Siloam | Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire | September 2018 – November 2018

- Creation of a database using MS Office Access
- Maintenance and management of the database
- Data entry of patients details and staff members

Lab Assistant | Methodist Secondary School of Cocody | Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire | September 2013 – June 2015

- Installation of Operating Systems i.e.: Microsoft Windows on lab computers
- Maintenance of defective devices
- Supervision of the students' usage of computers
- Provision of guidelines for the use of lab computers

Lab Assistant | Methodist Secondary School of Plateau | Abidjan, Côte d'Ivoire | September 2009 – June 2013

- Maintenance of lab computers
- Installation of gaming, office and multimedia software for the computer lab

- Supervision of students' usage of computers
- Provision of guidelines for use of lab computers

EDUCATION

University of Toronto | Coursera

Mind Control: Managing your Mental Health during COVID-19

(https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/Z8QHQMS2HVPL)

University of Michigan | Coursera

Introduction to Programming using Python

(https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/PH8KE9MYVX4S)

Python Data Structures

(https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/JG66F6WBVBAZ)

Strathmore University | Nairobi | Kenya

Bachelor of Business Information Technology (ongoing)

Diploma in Business Information Technology obtained in October 2021

Graduate School of Management | Abidjan | Côte d'Ivoire

VIP Coaching for IT in English obtained in April 2017

Nelson Mandela University (formerly Nelson Mandela Metropolitan University) | Port Elizabeth | South Africa

English Language Skill Certificate obtained in December 2016

Methodist Secondary School of Cocody | Abidjan | Côte d'Ivoire

Baccalaureate of Secondary Education in Math and Sciences obtained in July 2015

Methodist Secondary School of Plateau | Abidjan | Côte d'Ivoire

General Certificate of Secondary Education obtained in August 2012

SKILLS

Quality: Devoted, Engaged, Knowledge seeker, Teamwork and Good listener

Language skills: French (native language, written and spoken) – English (2nd language, written and spoken)

Hobbies: Football, Movies & Series, Travelling

IT: Mastery of the Microsoft Office pack (MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint and MS

Access), Developing skills on programming languages such as PHP, JavaScript, Oracle Database,

SQL server and Python

REFERENCE(S)

Richard Arina Okonda

Lecturer, French Department, Strathmore University P.O. Box 59857 00200 – Nairobi

Email: richmondarina@yahoo.com / Tel.: +254(0)733402912

Isaac Kigen Kipkosgei

Lecturer, School of Computing and Engineering Science, Strathmore University P.O. Box 59857

00200 – Nairobi

Email: ikigen@strathmore.edu / Tel.: +254(0)722408508